It's time to change seats.
This one seat change
flipped my mundane high school life
right upside down.
[I like you.]
Huh?
Is he...
pranking me?
Hold on.
What if that note...
wasn't a prank?
Ms. Komori?
Does that mean I got in his way?
He's got the brains and the looks.
He's the highest tier guy in our school.
If I actually did piss him off,
my high school career is over.
What are you doing?
It's the real deal.
That note was for you.
What?
If you want to know why I like you...
Well, you'll find out.
[Your bed hair, your hunched back]
[You never prioritize yourself]
Keep pointing out my bad traits.
I wasn't pointing out anything bad.
These are stuff I like about you.
You prioritize others,
even at your own expense.
Because you're kind.
Cheers to us.
[Adapted from Mashiroito's work of the same title]
Asamiya?
You said you liked me, but...
You meant as friends, right?
What do you think?
What sort of dream was that?
[Your bed hair, your hunched back]
[You never prioritize yourself]
These are stuff
I like about you.
Asamiya has since been relentless
with the sticky notes.
At the pace he's going,
he might fill an entire notebook
by the end of this semester.
Something good happen?
You don't normally wake up so early.
It's just one of those days.
See you later.
Wait.
You've got some hair sticking up.
I know.
Just leave it.
Huh?
See you.
Morning.
You kept your bed hair intact.
You said you wanted to touch it
once every three days.
If I had it my way, it'd be every day.
What's in the bag?
Just a small gift. Here.
Bread?
To make up for the one you got me.
It's only the store-bought stuff, though.
Asamiya?
When I die, put this in the coffin with me.
Just eat it. Bread doesn't last that long.
Fine. Thanks.
Also, feel free to pass me less notes.
I'm sure writing all that is a hassle.
I was already keeping myself in check.
Seriously?
Yeah, I still have lots more to say.
But if you want, I'll slow down the pace.
Thanks.
Asamiya's a kind guy.
I enjoy hanging out with him.
But there's one catch.
Something I didn't realize
until I'd become friends with him.
'Sup!
You came to school with someone?
Yeah.
Becoming friends with Asamiya
means interacting with his posse.
- Did you do the homework?
- No.
Didn't think so.
Yeah, you made that obvious enough.
Let me copy yours? Please?
Sakaki, you broke up with another girl?
Yeah. It didn't work out.
Dude.
How long did your longest relationship last?
Uh...
Two or three...
Months?
Weeks.
Bingo.
Their conversation sounds foreign to me.
So, Asamiya. Anyone on your mind?
Yeah.
Seriously?
- Who's the lucky girl?
- Yeah, I'm curious.
- Asamiya's into someone?
- What a shocker.
Let's leave it at that.
Have you found someone new, Sakaki?
Not really.
Hey, I could go for Mayama.
Huh?
It's fine, I swing both ways.
No, um...
Sorry, he's off-limits.
Dude, I was joking.
Yeah, obviously.
But if your preferences were flexible,
who'd you pick from this class?
Something up?
No.
Do you work out?
Nah. I sometimes run to the station, though.
That's impressive.
I'm practically a noodle over here.
I like you, noodle body and all.
Uh, thanks?
Wait.
Can you wear your jacket?
Huh?
But we're running laps today.
That's exactly why I'm asking.
Sweat makes your shirt go sheer.
I didn't bring my track jacket today.
Here, wear mine.
Don't let the other guys see your skin.
Who'd get worked up seeing that?
Me.
See you in the gymnasium.
Smells like Asamiya.
No. Weird thoughts, begone!
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Asamiya's definition of "liking" someone
isn't anything serious, right?
His posse certainly acts like
it'd be something casual.
Now pair up and stretch.
Yes, sir.
Uh...
Are you flexible?
Not at all.
Then I'll go easy on you.
Thanks.
Ow, ouch!
What happened to going easy on me?
Seriously, quit pushing!
No.
You're going to break something!
I'm gonna rip in half!
Let's test your limits.
Hey, quit it! Ow!
And swap.
Too bad.
Here I go.
Sure.
Are you even trying?
I'm giving it all I got.
Ever heard the phrase, "poetic justice"?
Huh?
Hey, pause. Seriously.
This is payback.
My bad.
Huh?
Yo, quit flirting over there.
Killjoys.
Shouldn't you run at your own pace?
I am running.
No, I mean...
Asamiya!
I know you can go faster! Pick it up!
See?
Wait for me. I'll see you in a lap.
Mayama, you've become best buds with Asamiya.
- You think?
- Yeah, you haven't noticed?
He spends more time with you than us now.
Give it to me straight.
What do you think of him?
Well...
I don't know.
I guess he feels far away?
Far away, huh?
- I'm beat...
- Mayama.
Asamiya's calling for you.
Huh?
Hey.
'Sup.
Sorry, did I do something wrong?
You were seriously miffed earlier.
Miffed?
I guess so.
I told you to wait.
Huh?
But you ran with Sakaki and Tsunekawada.
Don't leave me in the dust next time.
Sure.
I guess?
Is that why you called me here?
Huh? I thought you called me here.
Busted.
- Hey!
- Go for it, you two.
If Asamiya feels so far, then get close!
They locked us out.
It won't last long.
You're taking this easily.
I feel far away to you?
Uh, well...
You okay?
Yeah, the wind's just sort of chilly.
Mayama's looking cold, Asamiya.
Why not warm him up?
It's fine. I'm used to the cold.
Huh?
It'll get them to stop.
Do I still feel far?
Smells like you.
Stop, you'll cause a misunderstanding.
Yeah?
I mean...
You only "like" me
as a friend, right?
Like you "like" everyone else.
Of course not.
And cut!
That's enough flirting for today.
- Did you get a good shot?
- Sure did.
This is sure to do numbers.
Upload the video, and you're dead.
I was joking. You know I wouldn't.
Too bad.
I knew it.
We'd get crazy followers, though.
Asamiya?
I'm sending the video to my phone
before it's deleted.
Why?
I'll delete it if you want me to.
So long as it doesn't spread, it's fine.
It'll be my family heirloom.
Yeah, anything but that.
Mayama.
Got a moment?
Oh no.
Is this it?
Are they gonna beat me up?
Are they mad I took Asamiya away from them?
Mayama.
- We're sorry!
Huh?
Asamiya got seriously pissed at us
for our stunt this afternoon.
He said we took it too far.
Asamiya's not the most social guy, right?
So, it was surprising to see him trust you.
As his only other friends,
we were happy for him.
But we definitely spun out of control. Sorry.
You really don't have to apologize.
Mayama, can we be friends, too?
- Huh?
- Hang out with us.
Not just with Asamiya.
Well, I'm not really...
Okay. Sure.
- Awesome.
- Nice!
So, what's our next move?
Maybe we are the same.
I had put a line between us.
But now that we're actually talking,
I can see Sakaki and Tsunekawada
are just two normal classmates of mine.
And...
Do I still feel far?
Maybe Asamiya is, too.
Asamiya.
Chatting without me, again?
It's nothing that serious.
We were talking...
Because we're friends.
Sakaki and Tsunekawada are my friends now.
What's wrong with hanging out with them?
I don't want you restricting who I talk to.
Sorry.
I've got an idea.
Since the culture festival is coming up,
let's all join the planning committee
for our class.
Planning committee?
Brilliant idea.
Want in, Asamiya?
Sure.
Then that's that.
Let's start brainstorming our set-up.
What to do...
- Any ideas?
- The world's our oyster.
How about the classic maid cafe?
Dude, we're all guys.
Asamiya would look great in a maid dress.
- I can see it.
- Hell no.
Drop it.
Think of something else.
You weren't put off by the idea?
Huh?
The planning committee.
I hope we didn't force that on you.
You didn't.
You always look out for me like that.
Making sure I'm okay with whatever.
I'd never do something
you're not okay with.
Which reminds me, I hugged you earlier.
I'm sorry if that made you uncomfortable.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
You're really kind, Asamiya.
I take this road to the end.
See you tomorrow.
Asamiya's "like" was not as a friend.
Which means...
I have to give him a reply eventually.
I don't dislike Asamiya.
If anything,
I'm glad he likes me.
But...
If I had to give him a reply,
It wouldn't be a "yes".
I'm happy you feel that way.
But...
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Huh?
Dude, obviously we were joking.
She'd never confess to a guy like you.
Exactly.
You thought we were serious?
Yeah, she's totally out of your league.
I'm cracking up!
A guy like Asamiya...
is way out of my league.
I'm sure he's only feeling confused.
He'll eventually realize he was wrong.
Our class will be doing
a haunted house for the culture festival!
Is there someone who catches your eye?
We agreed Mayama would be a werewolf.
Cute.
Perfect.
Scare you?
Why do I like him so much?
But I'm sure about one thing.
Mayama is my first real crush.
Be more confident in yourself.
Here.
- Huh?
- Perfect for the name, "Hare", right?
This one's for you.
When you confessed to me,
I think I was happy.
It's just...
There's better people out there for you.
But I like 'you', Mayama.